Register to The Love Family Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Rogers, Francis, 1901-1916; 14 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rothwell, Walter Henry, 1920; typed letter signed (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Roy, Anton Van, 1903; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rubinstein, Arthur, 1921; 2 cards (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ruegger, Elsa, 1899-1912; 24 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ruegger, Elsa, 1909; 3 cards (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Safonoff, Wassily, 1907-1914; 11 autograph letters signed, 5 cards (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Salzedo, Carlos, 1921 Oct 29; typed letter signed (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Samaroff, Olga to Mrs. Seaver, 2 typed letters signed (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Samaroff, Olga to Helen Love, 1911-1919; 31 typed letters signed (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Samaroff, Olga to Franz Kneisel, 1917 Mar 10; typed letter signed (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Samaroff, Olga to Helen Love, 1911-1918; 2 autograph letters signed, card (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Saminsky, Lazare to Lucy Love, 1921 Oct 2; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Saminsky, Lazare to Helen Love, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Saminsky, Lazare to Helen Love, 1921 Oct 9; card (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sandby, Hermann, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schelling, Ernest, 1917-1921; 2 typed letters signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schelling, Ernest, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schindler, Kurt, 1913 Apr 4; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schnitzer, Germaine to Franz Kneisel, 1916 Jan 5; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schulz, Leo, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1930 Jun 27; typed letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1903 Mar 16; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schumann-Heink, Ernestine, 1929; 2 cards, 3 autographs, 3 callcards (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1901-1918; 6 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1933 Mar 10; typed letter signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1897-1922; 11 cards, 4 autographs (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sembrich, Marcella's secretary, 1931; 4 typed letters signed (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Seygard, Camille Fischer, 1899-1904; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare, Louise, 1900; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare, Louise, no date; card (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Shelley, Harry Rowe, 1898-1904; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Shelley, Mrs. Harry Rowe, 1898 Apr 18; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Smith, David Stanley to Mrs. Seaver, 1906-1911; 19 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Smith, David Stanley to Helen Love, 1913-1914; 6 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Smith, David Stanley to Franz Kneisel, 1914 Apr 6; autograph letter signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Gerrit, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Spalding, Albert, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spalding, Albert, 1921 Apr 30; card (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond to Mrs. Seaver, 1907-1911; 11 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond to Franz Kneisel, 1909-1910; 2 typed letters signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond to Helen Love, 1916 Apr 1; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spiering, Theodore, 1919 Apr 1; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Spiering, Theodore, 1921-1923; 2 typed letters signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Steinway, William, 1894-1895; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Steinway, R., 1901-1904; 2 autograph letters signed, card (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Sternberg, Constantin to Franz Kneisel, 1913 Feb 15; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sternberg, Constantin to Franz Kneisel, 1913 Mar 4; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Sternberg, Constantin to Helen Love, 1913; 3 typed letters signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stock, Frederick, 1910 Jun 1; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stock, Frederick, 1911; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stojowski, Sigismond, 1908 Dec 2; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stokowski, Leopold, 1912 Feb 1; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stransky, Josef, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stransky, Josef, 1920 Dec 5; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Svecenski, Louis to Helen Love, 1912-1926; 28 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Svecenski, Louis, 1923 Jul 19; 3 cards (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Swift, Samuel, 1898-1906; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tapper, Thomas, 1916; 2 typed letters signed (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tapper, Mrs. Thomas, 1912; 3 autograph letters signed, card (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tauscher, Hans, 1902 Nov 23; card (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ternina, Milka, 1904 Feb 29; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ternina, Milka, 1910 Feb 8; card (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ternina, Milka, 1896; 2 autographs (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, Theodore, 1902 Nov 7; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Thursby, Emma Cecilia, 1897-1930; 9 autograph letters signed, 6 cards (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tinlot, Gustave, 1921; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1934-1936; 2 autographs (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Townsend, Stephen, 1923 Sep 28; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Townsend, Stephen, no date; card (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Troostwyk, Isidore to Franz Kneisel, 1917 Apr 12; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Van Hoose, Ellison, 1902; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Verdi, Jean, autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vliet, Cornelino van, 1918 Oct 20; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vogrich, Max to Franz Kneisel, no date; card (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Waller, Henry, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Warlich, Reinhardt, no date; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Warren, George William, 1884 Oct 6; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Warren, Samuel Prowse, 1897; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Whithorne, Emerson to Franz Kneisel, 1915; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whithorne, Emerson to Helen Love, 1915-1916; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whithorne, Emerson to Helen Love, 1915; typed letter signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Arthur to Helen Love, 1904-1917; 12 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Arthur to Franz Kneisel, no date; 6 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Arthur to Mrs. Seaver, autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Arthur to Helen Love, 1912 May 14; card (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Whiting, Arthur to Helen Love, 1920 Dec 4; card (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Willeke, Willam to Helen Love, 1917-1921; 6 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Willeke, Willam, 1914-1917; 3 cards, 2 autograph programs, 3 notes (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Willeke, Willam, 1914; 2 signed bills (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Willeke, Victoria, 1915 Jul 12; card (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Mary Knight, 1888-98; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Zadora, Michael (Michal), no date; autograph letter signed (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, Series II
  - Ackenbach, Marie Louise, 1898 Oct 31; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Adamowska, Antoinette, 1898; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ardin, Leon, 1918 Dec 8; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baernstein, Jos., 1899; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Behrens, Mes. Conrad, 1896; 5 autograph letters signed, 2 cards (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Belinfaute, Estrela, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ben Greet, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Betti, Adolfo, no date; 4 autograph letters signed, card (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Beyer, Caroline, 1899 Apr 8; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bing, Rudolf, 1957 Jan 19; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bjorksten, Theodor, 1899; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bonucci, Arturo, 1921 Jan 25; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Brand, Tita, 1902-1903; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Breitner, L., no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bushnell, Ericsson F., 1895-96; 9 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cagin, Alfred, 1912 Jul 15; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cheney, Anne, 1898; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Christie, Winifred, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Christie, Winifred, 1916 Mar 24; signed bill (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cochran, J.W., 1900; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cole, Rossetter, 1921; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cracrofs, Mary to Franz Kneisel, 1911 Sep 26; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dricke (?), Wilhelm, 1915; card (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fremstadt, Olive, 1912 Dec 19; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Music Chorus members, no date; typed page (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ginebert (?), Yvette, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gorgoza, E., no date; autograph (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gorimson, Bonarius to Franz Kneisel, 1914 Apr 4; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hillmann, (?), 1899; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hinkle, Florence, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Horticus, (?), 1914-1915; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Horticus, (?), 1915; card (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Iuten, Ferdinand von, 1896; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Klafsky, Katharina, 1895-96; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Klafsky, Katharina, 1896; 2 autographs (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Koenik(?), 1909-1910; 9 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Leon, Oscar, 1917-1918; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Liszineska, Marguerite Melville, 1921; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Loeschigk, W.O., 1898-99; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mason, Mrs. Alfred Bishop, no date; card (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Meader, George, 1921; 3 cards (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Niedermann, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Novaes, Guiomar, no date; autograph program, 5 signed callcards (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Olitzka, Rosa, no date; 4 cards (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Oumiroff, Bogea, 1910 Jan 13; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Panel, Albert B., 1919; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Peterson, May E., no date; card (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Raymond, Annie Carry, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Reszke, Edouard de, 1900; autograph (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rummel, William Morse, 1911 May 11; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sameting, L., 1915; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Scharwenka, Mrs. Philipp, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Schenk, Elliott, 1920; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sealy, Frank L., 1899; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Seidl, Mrs. Anton, no date; card (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sickess, Jan, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Suten, Fred. von, 1910-1917; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tagliapietra, Arturo, 1917; card (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Urchs, Ernest, 1917; typed letter signed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Willemborg, Helene, 1899; autograph letter signed (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, various autographs (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Printed Matter and Miscellaneous, Series III
  - Newspaper clippings: German opera (Damrosch), 1894-1898 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings: German opera and others (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bauer, Harold: programs, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bauer, Harold: programs, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bauer, Harold: programs, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bauer, Harold: programs, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bauer, Harold: programs, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Printed matter (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Max Alvary, David Bispham, Lilli Lehmann, Marcella Sembrich, George Warren
  - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Flowers from wreath of Anton Seidl's funeral
    Leaves from Mendelssohn's grave
- Photographs, Series IV
  - Alvary, Max, no date; signed photograph, 4 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Alvary, Max's house, no date; 5 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Alvary, Max's tomb, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Alvary, Max's children, no date; 4 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Bauer, Harold, 1880-1922; 4 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Bauer, Harold, unsigned photograph (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Behrens, Conrad, 1896; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Bushnell, Ericsson, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Bispham, David, 11 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Bispham, David, 8 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cahier, Mme. Charles, 1926; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Campanari, G., no date; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Carreño, Teresa, no date; 4 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Derschurch, Fritz, 1897; 2 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Elman, Mischa, no date; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fischer, Emil, no date; 4 signed photographs, 3 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fischer-Seygard, Camille, no date; 3 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gadski-Tauscher, Johanna, 1897; 4 signed photographs (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gerardy, Jean, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gruening, ?, no date; 2 unsigned photographs (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hebelman, Theodore, no date; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hobbing, Heinrich, 1897; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hofmann, Josef, 1902; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hollaender, Alexis, 1903; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Huss, Henry Holden, no date; signed photograph (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Prof. Joachim, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kalisch, Paul, 1897; 3 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kneisel Quartet, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Kraus, Ernst, no date; 4 unsigned photographs, signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lange, Paul, 1896; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Letz Quartet, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lehmann, Lilli, 1899; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lhévinne, Josef, 1906; 3 signed photographs, 4 unsigned photographs (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lohse-Klafsky, Katharina, 1896-1897; 2 signed photographs, unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mannes, David, no date; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mason, William, 1904; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mead, Olive, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Melba, Nellie, 1898; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Morena, Berta, 1912; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Nordica, Lillian, no date; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan, no date; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Patti, Adelina, 1850-1860; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ruegger, Elsa, no date; 2 signed photographs, unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Safonoff, Josef W., 1909; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Samaroff, Olga, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Scharwenka, Xaver, 1897; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Schnick (?), Elliott, no date; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Schumann Heink, Ernestine, 1904-1933; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Seidl, Anton, 1892; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Sembrich, Marcella, 1899-1902; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Stehmann, Gerhard, 1897; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Stender, Frieda, no date; 2 signed photographs (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Szumowska, Antoinette, New York, May 5th; 1 signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ternina, (?), no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Thomas, Theodore, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Thursby, Emma, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Thursby, Emma, 1902; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Trethar, Chas F., 1905; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vollmar, Auguste, no date; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vopovrici, D., 1898; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Weingartner, Felix, no date; 5 unsigned photographs, signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1913; signed photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - York, Theodore van, no date; unsigned photograph (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, unidentified photograph (Box 11, Folder 11)